<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>&lt;think/></title><link>https://think.h-group.net/</link><description>Recent content on &lt;think/></description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>think@h-group.net (Dennis Hammer)</managingEditor><webMaster>think@h-group.net (Dennis Hammer)</webMaster><copyright>(c) dennis hammer</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://think.h-group.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On getting older</title><link>https://think.h-group.net/blog/on-getting-older/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>think@h-group.net (Dennis Hammer)</author><guid>https://think.h-group.net/blog/on-getting-older/</guid><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Quoting &amp;lt;a href=&amp;#34;https://www.katycowan.co.uk/blog/getting-old&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Katy Cowan&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;this really resonated with me today. Emphasis my own.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We were the kids who missed the first wave of acid house but still got swept up in the afterglow. We straddle the line between Gen X and Millennials — the so-called Xennials. We grew up analogue and came of age in the digital revolution. We spent more time climbing trees, riding bikes and playing football than we looked at any screen. We remember our landline numbers (mine had four digits), taping songs off the radio, and the thrill of a HMV shopping spree. We experienced life without social media, but we also remember getting our first Nokia and the magic of MSN Messenger. And we watched in awe as computers went from enormous desktop towers to sleek little rectangles we now carry around in our pockets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Quoting <a href="https://www.katycowan.co.uk/blog/getting-old">Katy Cowan</a></p>
<p>this really resonated with me today. Emphasis my own.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>We were the kids who missed the first wave of acid house but still got swept up in the afterglow. We straddle the line between Gen X and Millennials — the so-called Xennials. We grew up analogue and came of age in the digital revolution. We spent more time climbing trees, riding bikes and playing football than we looked at any screen. We remember our landline numbers (mine had four digits), taping songs off the radio, and the thrill of a HMV shopping spree. We experienced life without social media, but we also remember getting our first Nokia and the magic of MSN Messenger. And we watched in awe as computers went from enormous desktop towers to sleek little rectangles we now carry around in our pockets.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>We’re a small generation, often overlooked, but we’ve lived through more change than most—from mixtapes to Spotify, from faxes to WhatsApp, from digital revolution to AI. And because we existed in that liminal space, we carry a weird dual wisdom: we know how to live offline, but we can thrive online, too.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>So here’s what I try to remember, at any age: <strong>stay curious</strong>. Never assume you’re right. Read the newspapers you’d generally avoid. Challenge even your most cherished opinions. Try to see more than one side. You won’t always succeed, but it’s worth the effort.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Because if growing older has taught me anything, it’s this: <strong>certainty is overrated, and listening is wildly underrated.</strong> Cosy nights in don’t mean you’ve given up. They just mean you know what you like — and that maybe, just maybe, you never truly loved going to gigs as much as you pretended to. <strong>You stop performing. You stop pretending</strong>. And that’s freedom.</p></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Singapore</title><link>https://think.h-group.net/blog/singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>think@h-group.net (Dennis Hammer)</author><guid>https://think.h-group.net/blog/singapore/</guid><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today, I am flying to Singapore for the first time in about 6 years. Other than a number of work trips to India, I have not been back in Asia in a while. And to top it off, I am continuing to Manila on Monday for work meetings. Will be interesting to see how these places have changed. Manila - haven&amp;amp;rsquo;t been back there for over 10 years, but that will make its own blog post no doubt.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today, I am flying to Singapore for the first time in about 6 years. Other than a number of work trips to India, I have not been back in Asia in a while. And to top it off, I am continuing to Manila on Monday for work meetings. Will be interesting to see how these places have changed. Manila - haven&rsquo;t been back there for over 10 years, but that will make its own blog post no doubt.</p>
<p>Flying with SQ is always a blast from the past&hellip; I used to do that a lot, into all directions, but of course mainly between SIN and MEL on I think SQ227. Now on route to new, updated adventures.</p>
<p>The business class seat&hellip; I remember when it came out while I was stationed in Singapore. The size alone, epic. It&rsquo;s current incarnation feels a bit more cramped than my memory leads me to believe. But the bed is outright uncomfortable. Hard like lying on the floor, the temperature in the cabin too hot. Not the best sleep I had in a plane (that honor goes to Swiss First as well as LH Business).</p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>